CCG Base to 203,
（ＣＣＧ）
ＣＣＧ本部より203(ふたまるさん)号
we have reports of intruders in the
Aqua Building located in the 20th Ward.
20区 アクアビルディングに
不法侵入者との通報
（神代(かみしろ)利世(りぜ)）ああ…
Intruders are believed to be ghouls—I repeat, ghouls.
（ＣＣＧ）
不法侵入者は喰種(グール)　喰種と思われる
All units are to proceed on-site immediately.
至急 現場へ急行せよ
（リゼ）
ああ…　もっと もっと！
More! Give me more!
ん… おいしい
Delicious.
I guess they weren't exaggerating
when they called you a binge eater.
（ジェイソン）大喰(おおぐ)いってのは―
ダテじゃないみたいだね
You know, I hate it when
people interrupt me during a meal.
私 食事の
邪魔されるのって―
大嫌いなのよね
I suppose you haven't heard of me then?
（ジェイソン）
僕のこと知らないかなあ
Of course I have.
（リゼ）
知ってるわ
You're a hopelessly dull person with abhorrent tastes.
他人をいたぶるのが
趣味のつまらない男
ハハハ…　上の命令でね
I have my orders.
I've been told to take you back alive.
君を生け捕りにしろって
But you know...
でもさ その前に指の１～２本
Before I do that, I think I'll help myself to
a couple of fingers, an arm, or maybe even a leg or two...
腕の３～４本 脚の５～６本
You don't mind, do you?
もらっても いいよね
Such a small toy for such a big boy. I bet you like playing house.
（リゼ）
大きな体に小っちゃな おもちゃ
おままごとが好きなのかしら
How adorable.
かわいい
Allow me...
（ジェイソン）俺に奪わせろ
to remove them for you.
Give them back...
返せ　俺んだ
Those are mine!
Give them back!
返せえ～！
I'm not going to play with you.
（リゼ）
あなたとは遊んであげない
Several unidentified male bodies were discovered
（アナウンサー）昨夜未明
東京20区の商業施設ビル―
early this morning in the Aqua Building,
アクアビルディングで身元不明の
複数の男性遺体が発見されました
a commercial facility located in Tokyo's 20th Ward.
What is assumed to be ghoul saliva was retrieved from the bodies.
発見された
遺体からは―
喰種のものと思われる
唾液が残されており
"Aqua Building, a commercial facility in
Tokyo's 20th Ward"
Multiple Unidentified Bodies Found
The incident is being investigated as a criminal ghoul offense—
喰種による犯行と見て
捜査が行われております
（永近(ながちか)英良(ひでよし)）ハハハッ！
Is it actually that funny to you?
（金木(かねき)研(けん)）
そんなに笑うことないだろ
Egg of the Black Goat
Come on. You can't be serious about
going to a bookstore for your first date.
（ヒデ）だって お前
初デートで本屋はないだろ
Why not? She might be thrilled, you know!
なんで？
喜ぶかもしれないだろ？
For your information,
that's never going to happen. Period.
断言しよう　それはない
却下だ
What? Fine then, how about I take her
out to Big Grill instead, just the two of us,
ええ!?　じゃあ まず
ビッグガールで２人で―
and grab some burgers?
（カネキ）ハンバーグを食べ…
（ヒデ）ククッ ハハハ…
I'm being completely serious here!
まじめに答えたんだけど
No, no, it's great! That's so like you!
いや いい
お前らしくて いい
But when it actually happens, it'll be a total flop.
だが デートとしては失敗だ
What, you don't think I can handle it?
何だよ　ダメダメって
ヒデなら どうするんだよ
What would you do then, Hide?
Anteiku
Listen up. When it comes to dates,
you have to pick a place that excites the girl.
（ヒデ）
いいか デートっていうのは―
女の子が喜ぶ場所を
選ばなきゃいかん
Right. Such as?
（カネキ）例えば？
（ヒデ）えっ？　たっ… 例えば…
Huh? S-Such as...
You don't even know!
（カネキ）
ヒデだって知らないじゃんか
If I knew, I wouldn't be wasting my
afternoon here having a date with you.
（ヒデ）
知ってたら休日の昼間っから―
Predatory ghoul attacks in the 20th Ward
have been on the rise these last few days,
こうしてお前と
デートなんてしてないだろ
I suppose that's true.
（カネキ）そりゃそうだけど
with CCG's 20th Ward Branch announcing an investigation
（アナウンサー）
ＣＣＧ20区支部では―
"Aqua Building, a commercial facility in
Tokyo's 20th Ward"
Deaths Being Investigated as Ghoul Predation
into the possibility of a single
culprit for every incident so far.
同一犯による
捕食事件の可能性が…
That's pretty close, huh?
結構 近いな
In other news...
（アナウンサー）次のニュースです
So, what else have you got?
Who's the lucky girl?
The cutie you were talking about?
どの子だよ？　例のかわいい子
Oh?
（ヒデ）おっ あの子だろ
It's gotta be her, right?
No, it's not!
（カネキ）違うよ
I mean, she's pretty cute too...
（カネキ）確かに あの子も…
Excuse me!
（ヒデ）すいませーん
One cappuccino, please!
カプチーノ１つ
ああ カネキは？
And you, Kaneki?
I still haven't finished this.
One cappuccino.
（霧嶋(きりしま)董香(とうか)）カプチーノ１つ
（カネキ）僕は まだ
While we're at it, what's your name?
（ヒデ）あと お名前は？
（カネキ）ヒデ！
Hide!
It's Kirishima Touka.
霧嶋トーカですけど
Touka-san! Are you seeing anyone?
（ヒデ）
トーカさん！　恋人は？
Stop that, you idiot!
（カネキ）やめろ　バカ！
（ヒデ）フッ 愛らしい
She's so cute.
What'll I do if I end up getting kicked out!?
出入り禁止になったら
どうするつもりだよ
This shop is the only place where she and I both—
この店が僕と彼女の唯一の…
She's... the one.
（カネキ）その… 例の子が…
Don't even go there.
（ヒデ）諦めろ
（カネキ）えっ？
It'd be just like Beauty and whatever with you guys.
お前と彼女じゃ 美女と何とか
The Beast!
野獣だよ
Well then...
さーて
カネキが失恋したとこも拝めたし
Now that I've seen you lovelorn,
Egg of the Black Goat
I think it's time for me to head off.
そろそろ行くわ
Egg of the Black Goat
Wait— Hide...
ちょっ… ヒデ
See you later, Touka-chan.
（ヒデ）
またね トーカちゃん
Keep your head in the clouds, Kaneki!
（ヒデ）頑張れよ
（カネキ）えっ
カネキ妄想男！
ウフ…
I guess you struck the jackpot this time.
へえ
ラッキーなこともあるもんだな
Yeah. Who would've thought that
she'd like the same novelist as I do?
（カネキ）ああ まさか
好きな小説家が同じなんてね
Uh, what's-his-face, right? Takasaki Sen?
（ヒデ）
ああ 何だったっけ？ 高崎(たかさき)線？
It's Takatsuki Sen!
（カネキ）高槻(たかつき)泉(せん)！
We're going to hit the bookstore together this coming Sunday.
今度の日曜
一緒に本屋へ行くことになったんだ
Oh, yeah? I'm still not convinced
on the whole bookstore thing,
（ヒデ）
ほえ～　俺には本屋デートのよさは
ちょっと分かんねえけど―
but you go and have a good time.
楽しんでこいよ
Yeah.
I have to say though. This sure is getting ugly.
（中島(なかじま)康智(やすのり)）
しっかし ひどいありさまだったな
That's for sure.
Rumors say that they'll be fine
with eating just one person a month,
人 １人喰えば
１か月は もつって話だが―
but these binge eaters are something else.
大喰いは別格だな
They're like a bunch of wild animals, eating everything in sight.
（草場(くさば)一平(いっぺい)）
獣だって放っておいたら―
いくらでも
喰い続けるそうじゃないですか
Ghouls as animals, huh?
喰種は獣か…
On second thought, they're worse than livestock.
役に立たない分 家畜以下ですよ
That's true.
（中島）そうだな
Kaneki-san, what's your favorite work by Takatsuki?
（リゼ）
カネキさんは高槻作品で
何がいちばんお好きですか？
It would have to be his debut book.
やっぱりデビュー作かな
It was an instant bestseller after all.
新人離れした文体でしたものね
A refreshing delicacy amidst all the clutter, you might say.
過激さの中に
繊細さがあるというか…
Y-Yes, exactly. To be blessed with that much writing talent, releasing a bestseller whilst still in his teens—
そ… そうなんです
あの文章力で
デビュー当時は10代だなんて…
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか？
ううっ だ… 大丈夫です
I-I'm fine...
Er, I mean... That's...
あっ いや
あ… えっと その… あっ
Rize-san, you don't eat very much, do you?
リゼさんって小食なんですね
えっ？　あっ
実は その… ダイエットを
Actually, um, I'm currently on a strict diet...
Excuse me, I need to use the restroom.
（リゼ）すいません　お手洗いに
She's so refined...
女の子だ
Thank you very much for accompanying me today.
（リゼ）
今日は ありがとうございました
No, thank you. I-I had a great time.
（カネキ）こちらこそ
た… 楽しかったです
Actually, I kind of live near the recent
incidents that have been occurring lately...
（リゼ）
実は私… 最近 事件のあった
場所の近くに住んでいて
Oh, you mean the ghouls?
（カネキ）あっ 喰種の…
I'm quite squeamish when
it comes to these sorts of things.
（リゼ）
私 そういうの すごく苦手で―
I can't stop myself from trembling
whenever I think about it.
思い出すと
今も震えが止まらなくて
You'll be okay.
（カネキ）大丈夫
Please, rest assured.
I'll make sure to see you home safely.
安心してください
僕がちゃんと送りますから
Right, so then Hide asked me,
"Which do you like better, me or the novels?"
ええ　そうしたら ヒデが―
“俺と小説
どっちが大事なんだ”って
（リゼ）ウフフ…
おもしろい人なんですね
He sounds like quite the joker.
He sure is.
（リゼ）
本を好きになる きっかけとか
あったんですか？
What was it that sparked your passion for books?
（カネキ）父が残した本が
家にたくさんあって
My dad left a lot of his books behind.
物心つく前に
父を亡くしてるんです
I lost him before I could barely even walk.
I enjoyed the books he left behind,
その父の残した本が好きで―
so I spent a lot of my days reading
while waiting for my mom to come home.
母が働きに出ている間はずっと
本を読んで過ごしてたんです
Then, ever since she passed away...
母を亡くしてからは…
（カネキ）って こんな話
ヒデにしかしたことないのに…
You know, Hide is the only one I've ever told this to.
Is that right?
（リゼ）そうなんですね
あっ こっちです
It's this way.
（カネキ）あっ はい
Oh, okay.
（小坂(こさか)依子(よりこ)の鼻歌）
Touka-chan, what's up?
（依子）
トーカちゃん　どうしたの？
No, it's nothing.
ううん　別に
Well, we're pretty close now, so...
（リゼ）
もう すぐそこですから
Rize-san...
リゼさん　あの…
Um, if you wouldn't mind, can we go out again?
もし よかったら
また会ってもらえませんか？
Well, we do have similar tastes in books, and we share the same age...
私たちって
読書の傾向も似ているし―
年齢も同じだし
共通点 多いですよね
There's a lot we have in common, huh?
Kaneki-san...
（リゼ）カネキさん
（カネキ）あっ はい
Y-Yes?
The truth is, you caught my eye.
（リゼ）
ホントは私 気づいていたんです
I noticed you, the way you were looking at me...
あなたが私を見ていてくれたこと
Huh? Then, you're saying...
（カネキ）
えっ？ じゃあ リゼさんも…
Yes.
ええ　私も
あなたのことが好き
I, too...
happen to have fallen head over heels...
for you.
Ah, how delightfully exquisite!
ああ おいしい
Kaneki-san,
（リゼ）カネキさん
私 読書より好きなことがあるの
there's something I like even more
than reading. Would you like to know?
Tearing apart the luscious organs of someone
who isn't trying to escape from me is most enjoyable.
それはね 逃げまどう人の内臓を
ぜーんぶ引きずり出しちゃうこと
あ… ああ すてきよ　その表情
Yes, that marvelous expression!
Would you kindly allow me to...
もっと私を… ゾクゾクさせてえ～
thrill myself even more!?
No way! This can't be happening!
（カネキ）
ウソだ ウソだ ウソだ ウソだ
ウソだ ウソだ ウソだ
This can't be happening!
Tag, you're it!
（リゼ）つーかまえた　えい！
（カネキ）うわあ！
Kaneki-san!
（リゼ）カーネーキーさ～ん
ぐはっ！
I'm going to gently scramble up
your intestines for you now, okay?
おなか 優しく
かき混ぜてあげますからね
Oh, dead already?
あら？　死んじゃいました？
What a shame. I really did like you.
（リゼ）
残念　ホントに好きだったのよ
You have just the right amount of fat on you...
程よく脂も乗ってるし
柔らかくて食べやすそう
All nice and soft. A pleasure to eat!
How... could...
（リゼ）
なんで？　あ… た… が…
this...
（嘉納(かのう)）腹部内臓破裂
緊急オペを始めます
His abdominal organs are ruptured.
What's going on?
（カネキ）何だ？
Commence operating immediately!
Where... am I?
（カネキ）ここはどこ？
I thought I was on a date with Rize-san...
確か リゼさんとデートしていて
Prepare for an organ transplant!
（嘉納）臓器移植の準備を
Without consent from his family!?
（看護師）
遺族の方の同意なしでは…
Organ? Family?
（カネキ）臓器？　遺族？
一体 何の話だろう
What exactly are they talking about?
Doctor Kano!
（田口(たぐち)）嘉納先生！
（嘉納）すべての責任は私が取る
I will accept full responsibility!
Transfer her organs into him at once!
（嘉納）彼女の臓器を彼に
It's warm...
（カネキ）温かい　これは…
Is this...?
（カネキ）おかしい
一体 どうなっているんだ？
Something's not right...
What the hell is going on?
Kaneki-san!
（田口）カネキさーん
（田口）もう食べないんですか？
Is that all you're going to eat?
そうだ　お友達
今日もいらっしゃってましたよ
Oh, right. Your friend visited you again today.
あっ 嘉納先生
Ah, Doctor Kano...
How are we feeling, Kaneki-kun?
（嘉納）
調子はどうだい？ カネキ君
うーん　入院してから
何も口にしていないと聞いているが
I hear you haven't been eating
much ever since your admission,
but there doesn't seem to be
anything particularly wrong.
特に問題はないみたいだね
あの… 味覚が変なんです
Um...
My tastebuds... don't seem quite right.
味覚？
Tastebuds?
すべてが生臭いというか…
Everything just tastes like ash...
ああ… 精神的なものかもしれない
あれだけの事故だったから
That might be a psychological problem in itself.
It was a serious accident after all.
ハア…
There's no rush.
（嘉納）焦らないことだよ
ゆっくり治せばいいから
Take all the time you need to recover.
また来るよ
I'll stop by again later.
（カネキ）特に問題なし？
Nothing particularly wrong, huh?
It almost feels like the time I spent together with Rize-san
（カネキ）
あの日のリゼさんとの出来事が―
was only the product of some whimsical dream of mine.
全部ウソだったんじゃないかって
思えてくる
But if nothing else, there's one thing I'm certain of...
だけど 確かなのは
あれから 何かが…
Ever since then, something has been...
Something has been eating away at me.
何かが変だ
（ヒデ）
“カネキ　退院おめでとう”
Kaneki!
Congratulations on your discharge!
“我が家に余っていた
高級食材と―”
I present you with the finest leftovers my house
has to offer, along with your favorite hamburger.
“お前の大好きなハンバーグを
進呈しよう”
You better be grateful!
“感謝されたし　ワハハ…”
“追伸 全快したら
大学 戻ってこいよな”
P.S. When you're up to it, come on back to school.
“ボッチは つれえ”
It's rough here on my own.
ヒデ…
Hide...
（カネキ）
ありがとう　でも ごめん
Thanks,
but I'm sorry.
（小倉(おぐら)久志(ひさし)）そもそも喰種ってのは
こんな短期間に―
Well, in the first place, a ghoul has no need for
an appetite this large within such a short period of time.
大量の食事をとる必要がないんだよ
死体１つあれば 平気で
ひと月 ふた月 生きられる
Just a single dead body would ensure their survival for a month or two.
（アナウンサー）小倉さん
But Ogura-san, wouldn't the normal food that we eat suffice for ghouls as well?
喰種は人間と同じ食事では
満足できないんですか？
Can ghouls eat the same foods as humans?
Absolutely not, as ghouls are only able
to derive their nutrition from human organs.
（小倉）
ああ 喰種は 人からしか
栄養を摂取できないんだよ
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Not to mention, their tongues
function in a way different from ours, too.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
おまけに
舌のつくりが我々と違うから―
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
Ghoul Expert
Ogura Hisashi
Ghoul's tongues function
in a way different from ours.
人間の食べ物を食べると
めちゃくちゃ まずく感じるんだ
Should they attempt to consume human food,
they'd just be left with an incredibly awful aftertaste.
（小倉）舌のつくりが違うから
Their tongues function in a way different from ours...
めちゃくちゃ まずく生臭く
They'd just be left with an incredibly awful aftertaste...
（カネキ）そんな…
No way...
だあっ！
（ヒデ）お前の大好きな
ハンバーグを進呈しよう
I present you with your favorite hamburger!
（カネキ）ヒデ わざわざ
買いに行ってくれたのか
Hide...
Did you go out and buy this just for me?
（カネキ）ウソだろ…
This can't be happening...
Hide
Kaneki
（西尾(にしお) 錦(にしき)）友達か？
（ヒデ）はい
A friend of yours?
Yeah.
今日 退院したはずなんすけど
連絡つかなくて
He was supposed to be discharged today,
but he isn't picking up his phone.
I even went to his place several times,
見舞いも何度か行ったんすけど
追い返されちゃいました
but he wouldn't answer the door.
（ニシキ）ふーん
俺なら そんなクソ無礼なやつ
関係 切っちまうけど
I wouldn't even bother anymore
with a rude brat like that.
（ヒデ）
カネキはガキのころからの
親友っすから
Kaneki and I have been best friends since we were kids.
親友か
Best friends, huh?
（ヒデ）
もしもし カネキ？　体調どうだ？
Hey, Kaneki? How are you doing?
さっき 駅前の本屋で高槻何とかの
サイン会やってたから―
I was in front of the station
and saw Takatsuki what's-his-face
signing autographs at the bookstore, so I thought I'd hit you up.
教えようと思って
とにかく元気になったら
連絡しろよ
Anyway, give me a call when you're feeling better.
The
Takatsuki Sen
book signing
has ended.
ハア
（カネキ）
人… 人… 人… 人…
People... So many people...
People... These are people...
子供… 人… 人…
Children...
People, more people...
（カネキ）女… 少女… 男…
（女性の声）肉… 肉…
Woman...
Flesh...
Girl...
Man...
Flesh... Flesh... Flesh...
（カネキ）家族… 子供… 青年…
（女性）肉… 肉… 肉…
Family...
Children...
Boy...
Flesh, more flesh...
Woman...
（カネキ）女… 子供… 少年…
（女性）肉… 肉…
Child...
Flesh, I want flesh...
Boy...
（カネキと女性）
肉… 肉… 肉… 肉… 肉！
Flesh, I need flesh...
Flesh, so much flesh...
Flesh!
（女性）ちょっ… あの人
（男性）バカ　関わるなって
Hey, that man...
Don't get involved, idiot!
ぐう…
何だよ？
What the hell is this!?
I know what's happening!
（カネキ）原因は分かってるんだ
（嘉納）彼女の臓器を彼に！
Transfer her organs into him at once...
（小倉）
ナイフや包丁などの刃物では
傷１つ つかない
Blades such as knives or kitchenware cannot hurt them...
If that's true...
（カネキ）だったら だったら
だったら それを…
If that's true...
If this is really true...
Then surely, this will...
（カネキ）もう ほかに
どうしろって言うんだよ
What am I supposed to do now?
人を殺して… 肉を！
Flesh...
Murder a human... and devour their flesh!
あっ… 僕は何を…
こんなんじゃ まるで
What am I—
It's almost as if...
（カネキ）
この香りは… 初めて嗅ぐのに
どこか懐かしいような
That scent...
It's something I've never smelled before, but it seems so welcoming...
A sweet aroma, like Mom's home cooking...
まるで母さんの手料理のような
優しい香り
僕にも食べられる何かがある
There's something over there that awaits me,
something that even I can eat!
Where is it?
どこだ どこだ どこだ どこだ！
Where is it!?
近い　ハアハア…
It's close...
肉… ハアハア…
A ghoul...
（カネキ）喰種… 人間…
And a human!
死体の香りに
釣られていたなんて
How could I have been enticed here by the scent of a mangled corpse!?
You're a ghoul... right?
喰種… だよな？
What's the matter? Are you all right?
どうした？　大丈夫か？
My name's Kazuo.
俺 カズオっつーんだ
I haven't eaten for a while,
俺も久しぶりだから
あんまり分けてやれねえけど
so I can't share too much with you,
but here, help yourse—
（カズオ）ほれ喰いな
（ニシキ）どーん
ったく　俺の喰場(くいば)
荒らしてんじゃねえぞ
Seriously,
how about you leeches back
away from my hunting grounds?
あっ 見たことねえやつだな
Well, you're a face I haven't seen around here.
つーか なんで片目だけ赤いんだ？
気持ちわりい
More importantly, where's your
other red eye? That's kinda gross.
You know what happens when you get
caught on someone else's territory, right?
人のテリトリー荒らしたら
どうなるか分かるよな？
ち… 違う　知らなかった
N-No, I wasn't— I didn't know...
僕は たまたま
通りかかっただけで　ぐっ…
I just happened to be passing by...
（ニシキ）はい 想像して
Okay, imagine this.
Your girlfriend is naked and lying on the ground.
自分の恋人が裸で倒れている
There's a guy there with his pants down, he turns around and says to you,
そこに下半身丸出しで
こう言うわけ
"I wasn't doing anything. I just happened to be here."
“僕は何もしてません
偶然ここにいました”って
お前が言ってるのは
つまりは そういうこと
That's exactly what I'm getting from you right now.
（ニシキ）
俺なら殺しちゃうよ そんなやつ
If it were up to me, I'd blow his damned brains out.
だから殺す
俺の喰場を荒らした罰
That's why I'm going to kill you,
because you trespassed on my hunting grounds—
（トーカ）誰の喰場だって？
（ニシキ）あ？
Whose hunting grounds did you say?
（トーカ）
いつから あんたの喰場に
なったんだよ　ニシキ
Since when were these your hunting grounds,
Nishiki?
（ニシキ）トーカ
（カネキ）ぐわっ…
Touka...
She's dead, right? That binge eating woman?
（ニシキ）知ってんだよ
死んだんだろ？　あの大喰い女
だから ここは あんたの喰場？
And that gives you an automatic claim to this area?
リゼが奪った喰場は
力の弱い喰種たちに分け与える
Now that Rize's gone,
the responsibility of allocating hunting grounds
to the weaker ghouls and those at the 20th Ward
20区の管理は
うちら“あんていく”の仕事だろ
falls on Anteiku's shoulders.
Are you serious?
あんていくみたいな
ひよった連中に―
A bunch of fence-sitters like those of you at Anteiku have no right to make decisions for others!
ごちゃごちゃ言われる筋合いは
ねえんだよ
This was my hunting ground before Rize came—
もともと ここは俺の喰場だった
リゼが来るまでは…
Because you were too weak.
弱かったせいだろ
Getting told off by some younger,
overconfident little punk really pisses me off.
（ニシキ）
年下のクソ生意気なガキに―
コケにされるのって
すげえムカつくんだよな
Does it now?
あっそ
Enough is enough!
ほざけ！
浅いんだよ こんなの
You'll have to cut deeper than that!
（トーカ）そう
（ニシキ）あっ
Are you sure?
Should I cut a little deeper next time?
次は もっと強めでいい？
死体 持ってけ　もやし野郎
Take your corpse with you, coward.
欲しいの？
You want this?
（トーカ）食べないの？
You're not gonna eat?
o
shi
e
te
o
shi
e
te
yo
so
no
shi
ku
mi
wo
Tell me, oh tell me, the way this world works
つーか あんた
片目だけって 変わって…
Then again, only one of your eyes is like that...
bo
ku
no
na
ka
ni
da
re
ga
i
ru
no?
Just who is it that exists within me?
You're the one who was with Rize.
あんた　リゼと一緒にいた…
（トーカ）
なんで喰われてないの？
Why weren't you eaten? Wait...
でも その目…
That eye...
ko
wa
re
ta
ko
wa
re
ta
yo
ko
no
se
ka
i
de
In the midst of this broken, broken world
うっ… 助けてください
Please, help me!
信じてもらえないかもしれないけど
僕は人間なんです
I know you're not going to believe this,
but I swear I'm human!
ki
mi
ga
wa
ra
u
na
ni
mo
mie
zu
ni
you hollowly laugh without a backward glance
And yet...
なのに それを食べたくて…
食べたくて 仕方がなくて
I desperately want to eat that...
I want to devour it so badly that it aches...
But if I do...
でも そうしたら
もう人間ではなくなってしまう
I won't be human anymore!
If you're in that much pain, then eat.
そんなに苦しいなら喰いなよ
ko
wa
re
ta
bo
ku
nan
te
sa
i
ki
wo
to
me
te
Already broken down, I hold my breath.
ぐっ… イヤだ！
No way in hell!
イヤだ イヤだ イヤだ
I'll never do it! No way!
furi
izu
frozen
ko
wa
se
ru
ko
wa
se
nai
ku
ru
e
ku
ru
e
nai
You're vulnerable, unbreakable; irrational, yet sane
There's no way I can eat something like that, right?
a
na
ta
wo
mi
tsu
ke
ta
but I still find you
What is this? What is it to be a ghoul?
yu
re
te
yu
gan
da
se
kai
ni
ta
tta
bo
ku
wa
I stand here in this twisted and distorted world
Killing people, killing each other...
su
ki
to
t
te
mi
e
na
ku
tte
giving way to a hazy and empty void
I'm not like that!
I'm... human!
mi
tsu
ke
nai
de
bo
ku
no
ko
to
wo
mi
tsu
me
nai
de
Please don't look for me, my hidden self
This is ridiculous.
Why don't you just give in?
da
re
ka
ga
e
gai
ta
se
kai
no
na
ka
de
In this painted world of foreign whims
If you don't have the nerve to eat...
a
na
ta
wo
ki
zu
tsu
ke
ta
ku
wa
nai
yo
I never want to see you hurt
then I'll give you a hand!
o
bo
e
te
bo
ku
no
ko
to
wo
So please don't forget about me.
ma
chi
wa
ne
mu
re
do
In this sleepy city
ta
te
mo
no
wa
zu
tto
ke
n
se
tsu
chuu
sa
ta
te
mo
no
wa
zu
tto
ke
n
se
tsu
chuu
sa
the buildings get built higher and higher
to
shi
kei
kaku
sui
kou
chuu
under the eye of urban development
ka
mi
a
u
he
bi
ka
mi
a
u
he
bi
It's all a meshwork of snakes
mou
fingu
shi
ta
kan
jou
sen
morphing into a continuous loop
en
doru
fin
a
o
tte
u
ke
yo
Go
en
doru
fin
a
o
tte
u
ke
yo
Go
fueled by endorphins, they go, go, go
yo
ru
no
so
ra
ni
Under the night sky
jou
shou
su
ru
ta
ma
shii
the souls arise
kou
shin
to
kou
wa
jou
ki
wo
is
shi
ta
kou
shin
to
kou
wa
jou
ki
wo
is
shi
ta
in erratic parades of morality and faith
ku
i
zu
no
yo
u
da
ku
i
zu
no
yo
u
da
It's all one impossible quiz
ku
i
zu
no
yo
u
da
All one impossible quiz
ma
da
ka
ra
ppo
na
ashi
ta
wa
Tomorrow, the emptiness resumes
ka
gi
ri
na
ku
ro
ni
chi
kai
gurei
ka
gi
ri
na
ku
ro
ni
chi
kai
gurei
in an ever-dulling shade of grey
na
ni
ka
mo
na
re
zu
ni
In the future, the bleakness resumes
ka
gi
ri
na
ku
ro
ni
chi
kai
gurei
in an ever-dulling shade of grey
A
h
ko
n
ya
ki
mi
ga
ho
shii
no
sa
sei
ja
ta
chi
Tonight we will be the saints of your wishes
A
h
o
wa
ri
tsu
ge
te
ho
shii
no
sa
We will be the saints that prophesize the end
sei
ja
ta
chi
Saints
sei
ja
ta
chi
Saints
sei
ja
ta
chi
Saints
Yoshida Kazuo, 41-year-old ghoul.
Yoshida Kazuo
41 year old
— Ghoul —
そんなもの
喰(た)べられるわけがないだろ
Occupation: Fitness Club Staff.
（カネキ）
何だよ これ…　何だよ 喰種って
Occupation
Fitness Club Staff
人は殺す
仲間同士 殺し合う
On one of my days off, I received a hunting ground from Anteiku's Yoshimura-san.
僕は そんなんじゃない
So while I was at home, I sat my eyes on a target,
僕は人間なんだ！
killed it,
and was about to eat it.
（トーカ）
バカみたい
When suddenly a young ghoul appeared before me...
さっさと
諦めたらいいのに
Screaming
Screaming and shrieking—
signaling me to my demise.
喰べる勇気がないならさ
Off you go!
And then, my head was knocked off by Nishiki-kun.
私が手伝ってやるよ
Yoshida Kazuo, age of death: 41
Yoshida Kazuo
Age of death: 41
Next Time     "Incubation"
Former Fitness Club Staff.
Former Fitness Club Staff
Remains collected by Yomo-san
～♪